Stumblin' In
Our love is alive and so we begin
Foolishly layin' our hearts on the table
Stumblin' in
Our love is a flame burnin' within
Now and then firelight will catch us stumblin' in
Wherever you go
Whatever you do
You know these reckless thoughts of mine are followin' you
I'm fallin' for you whatever you do 'Cos baby you've shown me so many things that
I never knew
Whatever it takes baby
I'll do it for you
Our love is alive and so we begin
Foolishly layin' our hearts on the table
Stumblin' in
Our love is a flame burnin' within
Now and then firelight will catch us stumblin' in
You were so young oh and
I was so free
I may have been young but baby that's not what
I wanted to be
Well you were the one
Oh why was it me 'Cos baby you've shown me so many things that
I've never seen
Whatever you need baby you've got it from me
Our love is alive and so we begin
Foolishly layin' our hearts on the table
Stumblin' in
Our love is a flame burnin' within
Now and then firelight will catch us stumblin' in
Stumblin' in
Foolishly layin' our hearts on the table
Oh stumblin' in
Mmh stumblin' in
Now and then firelight will catch us stumblin' in
Oh stumblin' in
I'm stumblin' in
Foolishly layin' our hearts on the table
Stumblin' in
Oh oh stumblin' in
Oh stumblin' in
Ah stumblin' in
We were stumblin' in
Now and then firelight will catch us stumblin' in